[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 2006, it was confirmed that there are 9 planets in the Solar System.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Gastro is a common medical prefix, derived from the Greek word gastros which means what?", "correct_answer": "Stomach", "incorrect_answers": ["Gas", "Brain", "Cell"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The deficiency of what vitamin causes Rickets and Osteomalacia in humans?", "correct_answer": "Vitamin D", "incorrect_answers": ["Vitamin B5", "Vitamin A", "Vitamin E"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the green ghost captured first by the Ghostbusters in the 1984 comedy movie Ghostbusters?", "correct_answer": "Slimer", "incorrect_answers": ["Oozy", "Gozer", "Zuul"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these wombat species is also known as Coarse-haired Wombat?", "correct_answer": "Common Wombat", "incorrect_answers": ["Southern Hairy-nosed Wombat", "Northern Hairy-nosed Wombat", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the meaning of the word taco, denoting a traditional Native American meal?", "correct_answer": "Plug", "incorrect_answers": ["Bundle", "Cake", "Bracelet"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the high school in the movie American Pie?", "correct_answer": "East Great Falls High", "incorrect_answers": ["Lincoln High", "East Smith High", "American High"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "He was the founder of the Red Army, as well as a founding member of the Politburo.", "correct_answer": "Trotsky", "incorrect_answers": ["Kerensky", "Potemkin", "Lenin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How do you say, This is a robbery in Spanish?", "correct_answer": "Este es un robo", "incorrect_answers": ["Robo un es este", "Este robo es un", "Este es robo un"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed the 2006 movie The Pursuit of Happyness?", "correct_answer": "Gabriele Muccino", "incorrect_answers": ["Will Wang", "James Brooks", "Tim Robbins"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was in total eclipse according to Bonnie Tylers 1983 hit?", "correct_answer": "The heart", "incorrect_answers": ["The soul", "The moon", "The Sun"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed the horror film House of 1000 Corpses?", "correct_answer": "Rob Zombie", "incorrect_answers": ["Rob Schnider", "Rob Reiner", "Robbie Williams"]}]